What the hell is wrong with these eggs?
My stand.
I haven't the vaguest idea what it is,
but it's painfully clear that
it's no longer Pale Snake.
What is it?
What could it be?
I feel terrible something is quickly
raging out of control inside of me
there's some kind of independent power
that's ignoring my will but oddly
i feel hope in this power hope in
fact is the one and only thing i feel
from it dio's note recorded in
jotro's memories perhaps that is what
i need to control this power then
the time and place north latitude 28
degrees 24 minutes west longitude 80
degrees 36 minutes delightful heaven
appears to be there after all and
that place is at cape canaveral space
center to be precise at the beginning
of everything there was gravity.
Even this round earth of ours was
brought into reality with gravity.
No way!
We're gonna keep falling!
We're not falling down!
We're falling backwards!
No, this can't be.
Is this the Priest's new ability?
Jolene!
Here, you grab hold of Emporia!
Tybar, drive!
Hermes!
And with its gravitational pull, the
earth continues to revolve around the sun.
The question that still remains
is where on earth am I headed now?
What is going to happen next?
I knew my old man sealed away some
sort of ability in Egypt 20 years ago.
But this is insane!
This must be the heaven the
priest has been searching for!
Within my body and spirit
lies the existence of gravity.
And it shall also exist
at the end of the world!
There's our way into the visitor center.
Jolene, are you sure the priest
is still in this direction?
He's close, yeah.
I can sense him right here.
It almost feels like he was
just standing in this spot.
This is the priest's stand?
Is it in a new form?
Destiny is mine.
If I'm afraid of all my
future? As long as I can,
Sugar's red and white.
I'm going to go over the pain!
Thank you.
What's up with my hand?
I've come to eliminate you for good,
since you couldn't wait two more days.
Jolene Kujo.
My arms turning inside out! Jolene!
Hey, are you okay?
Are you the friend who was
aiding Jolene in prison?
Go, Emporio!
Hurry up and run to where Anastasia is!
Stone Ocean!
Jolene!
He's circled behind you!
First order of business.
Dispels of Jolene Cujo.
Anastasia, hurry up and come over here!
What in the world is this?
It's like your hair turned
in on itself, Jolene.
And so did my cleats.
It must be his attacks like from when his
fist grazed us but it barely made contact.
So if he punches us
we'll be in big trouble
gravity judging by everything
that's been Happening
around us this probably
has to do with gravity too
jolene whether it be an
apple or the Planet itself
everything on earth is
affected by gravity and all
of it is pulled towards
the earth's Gravitational
center that's the natural
law of the universe
except this guy's Ability
messes with that it
makes the gravity go in
the opposite direction
That's why whenever his
stance fists make contact
with something it'll be
Inverted and I don't know
how far but with everything
sideways we're gonna
Keep falling so this is
it thanks to the unique
energy around cape canaveral
the Priest has somehow
developed a new stand
it's no longer pale snake
which to have the ability
to manipulate memories.
Nor does it have the ability to split itself
in half infinitely like the green baby.
Jolene!
He's coming back around!
I need you to jump toward Anastasia!
Now, Emporia!
Whoa, she did it!
Are you kidding me?!
It's inverting!
Jolene!
No way, that's impossible!
Don't panic, Emporio.
You don't have to get so upset.
If I get turned inside
out every time he hits me,
then that just means I'll
have to let him hit me again!
so i can flip myself back to normal
so he can invert me all he wants to
because i'll just hit
him with the reverse!
you're okay?
oh good freaking grief!
give me a break!
it does the job but i still have to
sew my wounds back up with my thread!
although thanks to that there's
one thing i'm sure of Lucky for us,
as long as we can hit
him, he'll take damage.
It's looking like I should finish
this guy off right here and now!
I can't be babysitting!
Go, Emporio, start climbing!
Make your way up to that handrail!
I'm not here for you.
I'm here to make sure my darling
Jolene is back up if she needs it!
Go, go, go, go!
Polna, no!
This ticket box you're clinging on to
has already been turned inside out.
What's up with his movements?
Judging by its power, I thought it
would be an automated pursuit stand?
but his attacks are way too precise.
And he's not focused on attacking
my arms or legs anymore,
like he knows it's useless so he's
only pinpointing my vital areas
like my face and chest knowing
that if his fists touch me there
it'll be fatal plus he dodged my
kick and managed to get out of the
way by just millimeters which means
this is a remote control stand
the priest has to be around here
watching with his own eyes in other
words his stands movements are so
accurate because he's watching every?
attack.
This guy's stand causes destruction
by manipulating gravity,
so it just seems like he's powerful.
Where is he?
I thought Poochie would be hiding far
away, but I get the sense that he's a
lot closer than I realized.
He's somewhere close by with
a clear view of the area.
Hyperdrive!
Stay out of this.
Anastasia!
I already told you I'm
here to dispose of Jolene.
You are nothing.
Anastasia!
Jolene!
Stone oceans!
Ah!
No, Jolene!
The hell, Jolene?
What are you doing? Anastasia!
I bet if you tried, you could probably jump
onto the tiles on the side of the road.
But for right now, don't
let go of that rope, okay?
With your weight tightening the
rope, his stance being held down?
and getting the life choked out of him!
And he doesn't have the
power to fight back!
He's completely defenseless!
No freaking way!
Stan's desperately trying
to grab onto Jolene's
rope with his hands before
it gets choked to death!
If this thing manages to get a hold of
those threads of yours with its hands,
Jolene,
the rope's gonna get
inverted and break away!
Get that rope off of his
neck, Jolene! Do it now!
This was a distraction!
I did it so you could get away from him!
I can't, Anastasia!
There's no way I'm running
away from this now!
With this rope around its neck, we
finally have a chance to end him!
And for the record, I'm not
actually trying to choke it.
I'm just trying to get closer so
I can pummel it into the pavement!
What exactly are you saying, Jolene?!
If he lays even a finger
on your thick rope
and ends up inverting
everything attached to it,
that means your entire arm is gonna be
turned inside out and blown into pieces!
Son of a bitch!
Just you wait.
I'm going to climb over
there right now to get you.
Jolene isn't the type of person to
give up, even if we tell her to stop.
And this situation is
crazy. What the hell?
If you're going to go, then do it quickly!
Hurry up and get your foot out of
that metal frame before it's too late!
No, we've grabbed the rope already!
Not yet!
I still have time!
My thread can still hold out!
I won't cut it until I have to!
This is Sigma Team reporting.
It's no use.
We can't advance any further.
Our vehicles have been flipped over.
All our attempts to
head towards the visitor
center have resulted in
our trucks being flipped.
What's going on?
What do you mean, flipped over?
Explain the situation.
It's like I told you.
They got flipped.
Some sort of force is
turning over our vehicles.
I have no idea why, sir.
We're going to need a scholar or
a specialist to make sense of it.
Don't tell me you have no idea.
Rescuing the survivors is our duty.
Now figure it out.
Yeah, but sir, we really
don't know what's happening.
The extent of damage done and the number
of casualties or survivors are all unknown.
Debris is scattered everywhere.
What in the hell happened here?
It's as if a massive hammer came down from
the sky and smashed everything to shit!
This road's been turned into a junkyard!
This is Jayhawk 9.
We're about three kilometers away from
the visitor's center and have eyes on.
We're moving in to
locate any survivors now.
Whoa, what is this?
Which way is up?
Mayday! Mayday!
J-Hawk Nine!
Report your status!
J-Hawk Six, respond!
She does have a point.
This situation is our chance
to defeat the Priest's Stand.
But maybe not.
It's too much of a risk.
Jolene's arm is getting closer and
closer to crumbling in the pieces.
If you're going to make
your way to him, then hurry!
Take your shot and kill
this bastard already!
Oh, no shot!
He's trying to turn the frame inside out!
If he manages to do that, he'll
lift himself back up and be free!
Now move on!
Hurry up and ram his ass!
There's no use!
He's already getting up!
Now the stand has flipped
the tiles over again, too!
No, he grabbed onto it!
Stop, Jolene!
Get your throat off its neck right now!
You have to run away!
If you don't, your arm
is gonna get torn apart!
Dive or try!
I went ahead and took the liberty of
phasing Diver Drive into the rope.
So,
instead of the thread being turned inside
out and Jolene suffering the consequences,
the responsibility of taking
that affliction falls to me.
Anastasia.
Just keep going, Jolene.
As long as your rope is tightly wrapped
around that son-of-a-bitch's throat,
I'll make damn sure that its body
doesn't get it for even a second.
Anastasia! Do it!
Finish this guy off!
Now, Jolene!
I knew I should have disposed
of you when I had the chance,
no matter what it might have cost.
Back at the very beginning,
when we met in the prison,
our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ was
fated to be crucified on the cross.
Just as the Holy Mother Mary
was fated to lose her son.
In order for human beings
to attain happiness,
they must first overcome their destiny.
And the obstacles Dio and I must overcome.
Are you damned Joestars in your bloodline?
Wait, it can't be!
The priest himself was
here the whole time?
The reason I have come is to save my stand
from you while it's still incomplete.
It's complete.
What now?
Why am I lifting towards the sky?
My body is the gravitational center.
From where my feet are grounded,
gravity is pulled in reverse.
And the closer you get, the
stronger the pull becomes.
All I have to do now is wait
for my stand to become complete.
As it is, my ability is still too weak.
It must finish its evolution.
Anastasia, pull Jolene down with her rope!
I'm already trying!
Listen closely, my stand.
In order to turn them
inside out you must only hit
them one time I'll say it
again only hit them one
time don't waste time
targeting places like her
arms or legs only deal one
punch without exception.
All right, let's head back.
We'll continue waiting
in the visitor center.
What the hell?!
This battle is over.
Jolene can no longer feel any pain or have
the ability to use cognitive functions.
Her heart has been turned inside out.
The blood meant for her brain
should also be flowing in reverse.
Keep on pulling, Anastasia!
Hey, hurry up!
Pull Jolene's body back down here!
Jolene's thread's pulling apart!
No way!
No!
It can't be!
Jolene!
It will need a name.
I'll call this new ability Seamoon.
Invincibility.
Is that the power I've obtained even
before the coming of the new moon?
However, I must keep on telling myself it
is not power which I desire. But rather,
what I truly long for is
the ultimate happiness
that every human being has
the potential to achieve.
And Jolene Kujo was merely a
sacrificial pawn towards that end.
The same goes for Weather
and the other prisoners who
valiantly gave their lives to
further my righteous objective.
Their sacrifice was necessary.
No!
There's just no way!
What do we do now?
Jolene!
I can't believe that!
Just isn't possible!
What?
What's that sound?
My phone!
But how?
It wasn't working before.
I got a text message.
But who was it from?
My calls aren't going through.
The gravitational anomaly seems to
have sent a satellite out of orbit.
Are you Emporio?
I don't know exactly what's going on.
But I can sense that my daughter
and the priest have met.
Wait...
could this text be from...
could it be...
the person who said this?
Jolene is alive, but she's not safe.
Protect Jolene.
Just until I arrive!
That's all I ask.
She must have discovered
how to counter his gravity.
That's the only way she
could have survived.
She's alive, but just barely.
Jotaro Kujo.
Yeah, it is Mr.
Jotaro He must be close by
I...
I can't believe it
Jolene's actually still alive.
Then that means!
Could it be?
Anastasia you gotta find Jolene.
I think that Jolene is still alive.
For real!
Yeah but that also means that!
That pooch he'd lose.
Since he has the same
ability to sense her!
He's aware that she's still alive too.
What's going on?
Jolene Kujo.
Her heart should have
been turned inside out.
My gravitational power!
Should have destroyed it completely.
How in the world is she still alive?
What did she do?
I have to put an end to this.
The Joestar bloodline is something I
must overcome, no matter what it takes!
Dive or drive!
Which way are you going?
Take a guess.
In order to protect Jolene, I'm gonna
have to kill that fucking priest!
My head is filled with hope.
Of some place other than here.
Although you think I smile.
Inside and all the while.
I'm wondering about my destiny.
I'm thinking
about all
the things I'd like to do?
In my life,
I'm a dreamer,
a distant dreamer,
dreaming far
away from today.
Thank you.